Guide to the Stanford University, Libraries, Records SC0112
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional records, Accession ARCH-2002-221
  - ARL/AAU Research Projects (Box 4)
  - ARL-RECON (Box 4)
  - Articles (Box 4)
  - Backlogs (Box 4)
  - Big Heads (Box 4)
  - Big Heads (Box 4)
  - Big Heads (Box 4)
  - Big Heads (Box 4)
  - BARRnet (Box 4)
  - Bewley, William (Box 4)
  - Blackwell Science (Box 5)
  - Blackwell North America (Box 5)
  - Blois, Richard M. (Box 5)
  - BMG/Victor Project (Box 5)
  - Book Club of California (Box 5)
  - Book Expenditure Reports (Box 5)
  - Book Publishers/Book Sellers (Box 5)
  - Bookstore Expenditures (Box 5)
  - Bootstrap (Box 5)
  - Book Venders (Box 5)
  - Branner Earth Sciences (Box 5)
  - Brazil (Box 5)
  - Bread of Days (Box 5)
  - Breakfast Meetings (Box 5)
  - Brechin, Gray (Box 5)
  - Brent, Paul (Box 5)
  - British Library (Box 5)
  - Brown Building Storage (Box 5)
  - Building 160 (Box 5)
  - Buckwell, John (Box 5)
  - Building Projects (Box 5)
  - Bldg. Projects Mgr. (Box 5)
  - Bldg. Services (Box 5)
  - Bush, George (Box 5)
  - BuyPay (Box 5)
  - Cable (Box 5)
  - C-ACIS (Box 5)
  - C-ACIS (Box 5)
  - Cal/PALs (Box 5)
  - CA Digital Library (Box 5)
  - California Historical Society (Box 5)
  - California Library Association (Box 5)
  - California Library (Box 5)
  - C-ACIS (Box 5)
  - Budget (Box 5)
  - Blackwell (Box 5)
  - Blute, Richard (Box 5)
  - Book Sales (Box 5)
  - Briggs, Mitzi (Box 5)
  - California Library Services Board (Box 6)
  - California State Library (Box 6)
  - California State Library (Box 6)
  - California State Library (Box 6)
  - California State Library (Box 6)
  - California State Library (Box 6)
  - California State Library (Box 6)
  - California State Library (Box 6)
  - California State Library (Box 6)
  - California State Library (Box 6)
  - California State Library (Box 6)
  - California State Library (Box 6)
  - Cambridge University Press (Box 6)
  - Camis (Box 6)
  - Cash Awards (Box 6)
  - California State Library (Box 6)
  - Capital Equipment (Box 6)
  - Capital Projects (Box 6)
  - Card Catalog (Box 6)
  - Catalog Department (Box 6)
  - Catalog Department (Box 6)
  - Catalog Department (Box 6)
  - Catalog Department (Box 6)
  - Catalog Department (Box 6)
  - Catalog Department (Box 6)
  - CCC (Box 7)
  - Catalogue Department (Box 7)
  - CDG Meetings (Box 7)
  - CDP/Germanic (Box 7)
  - Cell Press (Box 7)
  - Censorship (Box 7)
  - Center for East Asian Studies (Box 7)
  - Center for International Security and Arms (Box 7)
  - Center for Prof. Development (Box 7)
  - Center for Research Libraries (Box 7)
  - Center for the Book (Box 7)
  - Central Circulation (Box 7)
  - Central Library (Box 7)
  - CETH (Box 7)
  - Channel 51 (Box 7)
  - Change Support at Stanford (Box 7)
  - Chemistry (Box 7)
  - Chem Library Classroom Project (Box 7)
  - Chen, Pau-Sen (Box 7)
  - Chicano Archives (Box 7)
  - Chicano Curator (Box 7)
  - Chico State University (Box 7)
  - Christmas Card (Box 7)
  - CIN (Cooperative Information Network) (Box 7)
  - Circulation Automation (Box 7)
  - Circulation (Box 7)
  - Circulation Services Interviews (Box 7)
  - CLASS (Box 7)
  - Classrooms, Tech Study on (Box 7)
  - Classics (Box 7)
  - Classics Department (Box 7)
  - Classics Department (Box 7)
  - Center for Research Libraries (Box 7)
  - Catalog Department Backlogs (Box 7)
  - CD-Rom (Box 7)
  - CLIR (Box 8)
  - CLIR (Box 8)
  - CLR Grant Proposal (Box 8)
  - CLU (Box 8)
  - Colby, Ed (Box 8)
  - CLIR/IMLS Conference (Box 8)
  - Collections (Box 8)
  - Collection Progress Review and Report (Box 8)
  - Collection Management and Development (Box 8)
  - Collection Management and Development Committee (Box 8)
  - Collections Program (Box 8)
  - Collections Program (Box 8)
  - Collection Review Program (Box 8)
  - Collection Review Program (Box 8)
  - Colloquium (Box 8)
  - Colophon (Box 8)
  - Columbia (Box 8)
  - CLR Conspectus Paper (Box 8)
  - Collections Department (Box 8)
  - CLIR (Box 8)
  - CNI (Box 8)
  - Collection Development (Box 8)
  - Collection Development (Box 8)
  - Ctr. For Integrated Systems (Box 9)
  - Columbia University Library (Box 9)
  - Compensation (Box 9)
  - Commercial CATV (Box 9)
  - Committee on Preservation and Access (Box 9)
  - Committee on the Libraries of the University (Box 9)
  - Committee Use and Communication (Box 9)
  - Compensation for Staff (Box 9)
  - Computer Serveys (Box 9)
  - Computing and Communication Facilities (Box 9)
  - CONOCO (Box 9)
  - Conservation Fundraising (Box 9)
  - Conservation Office (Box 9)
  - Contingency Planning Statements (Box 9)
  - Continuing Studies (Box 9)
  - Controller's Office (Box 9)
  - COPICO Photocopy (Box 9)
  - Cornell University (Box 9)
  - Correspondence (Box 9)
  - Creative Thinking (Box 9)
  - Creative Writing Program (Box 9)
  - CSUMB - Monterey (Box 9)
  - CSU Sacramento (Box 9)
  - CTL (Box 9)
  - Culpepper Foundation (Box 9)
  - Current Periodicals and Microtext Section (Box 9)
  - CWIS/CWIN (Box 9)
  - Commission on Preservation and Access (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, Misc. (Box 9)
  - Computer Science Tecnhical Reports (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, Misc. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, Misc. (Box 9)
  - CTTL (Box 9)
  - CRL (Box 9)
  - Commision on Preservation and Access (Box 9)
  - Committee on Committees (Box 9)
  - Communications Task Force (Box 9)
  - CONSER (Box 9)
  - Conservation Endowment Campaign (Box 9)
  - Cost Study (Box 9)
  - Council on Library Resources (Box 9)
  - Courtney, Professor (Box 9)
  - CRAM (Box 9)
  - CRAM (Box 9)
  - Cubberly Funds (Box 9)
  - Data Files (Box 10)
  - Data Services (Box 10)
  - DBMS Proposal (Box 10)
  - DCCS (Box 10)
  - Deacidification (Box 10)
  - Dean's Council (Box 10)
  - Dechma (Box 10)
  - Deferred Analytics Projects (Box 10)
  - De Guigne, Christian (Box 10)
  - Departments (Box 10)
  - DICE Issues (Box 10)
  - Digital Reference Library Networking Group (Box 10)
  - DIIT (Box 10)
  - Director's Retreat (Box 10)
  - Disability Resource Center (Box 10)
  - Disney (Box 10)
  - Distance Education (Box 10)
  - Distinguished Service Awards (Box 10)
  - Distributed Computing Environment (Box 10)
  - Diversity in SUL (Box 10)
  - Docents (Box 10)
  - Document Linker (Box 10)
  - Domestic Partners (Box 10)
  - Doyle, John (Box 10)
  - Draft Computer Policy (Box 10)
  - DSL (Box 10)
  - DRL files (Box 10)
  - Earthquake, Oct. '89 (Box 10)
  - Earthquake Preparedness (Box 10)
  - East Palo Alto Project (Box 10)
  - Eco, Umberto (Box 10)
  - EDI (Box 10)
  - EditEur (Box 10)
  - EducomTrustees/Officers (Box 10)
  - Electronic Imprint (Box 10)
  - Electronic Journals (Box 10)
  - Electronic References (Box 10)
  - Diane Walker (Box 10)
  - DECathena Deployment Research Program (Box 10)
  - Decision Support System Project (Box 10)
  - Department of Education (Box 10)
  - E-mail Abusers (Box 11)
  - Emergency Procedure (Box 11)
  - Emeritus Correspondence (Box 11)
  - EMS Migration Implementation (Box 11)
  - Encina Storage (Box 11)
  - Encyclopedia Britannica (Box 11)
  - Engineering (Box 11)
  - Engineering (Terman) Library Space (Box 11)
  - Engineering (Terman) Library Space (Box 11)
  - English Department (Box 11)
  - English and American Literature Curator (Box 11)
  - Environment Health and Safetly Training (Box 11)
  - EPA Project (Box 11)
  - EPRINT (Box 11)
  - E-Publishing (Box 11)
  - E-Publishing (Box 11)
  - Equipment (Shelving, Stands, Etc.) (Box 11)
  - Ergonomics (Box 11)
  - Ergocare (Box 11)
  - Eshoo, Anna (Box 11)
  - Ethics (Box 11)
  - ETV CO. (Box 11)
  - Exhibit Case Design Guidelines (Box 11)
  - Exhibits Shown at Green Library (Box 11)
  - Expert Partners (Box 11)
  - Facilities (Box 11)
  - Facilities (Box 11)
  - Facilities FY 1995 (Box 11)
  - Faculty Club - Membership Committee (Box 11)
  - Facilities Planning (Box 11)
  - Facilities Project (Box 11)
  - Facilities Project Management (Box 11)
  - Faculty / Technology (Box 11)
  - Falconer Biology Library (Box 11)
  - Falconer Biology Library Search (Box 11)
  - Falconer Library (Box 11)
  - F Miscellaneous (Box 11)
  - Flenner-Jones Memorial Fund (Box 12)
  - Flexible Classroom (Box 12)
  - Field, Charles D. (Box 12)
  - Field, Charles D. (Box 12)
  - Field Room (Box 12)
  - Flood 1986 (Box 12)
  - Flac (Box 12)
  - Folio (Box 12)
  - Folio (Box 12)
  - Folio (Box 12)
  - Food Research Institute Library (Box 12)
  - FRI (Box 12)
  - Fore Edge Paintings (Box 12)
  - Foreign Visitors (Box 12)
  - Forum Higher ED (Box 12)
  - Fraud, Losses due to (Box 12)
  - Functional Assignments (Box 12)
  - Furniture Orders (Box 12)
  - Gainsharing (Box 12)
  - GBALC (Box 12)
  - GCMP 4 Grant (Box 12)
  - German Visitors (Box 12)
  - Gift and Exchanges (Box 12)
  - Goals and Objectives (Box 12)
  - Goldsmith's Kress Library of Economic Literature (Box 12)
  - Government Documents (Box 12)
  - Government Documents, Staffing (Box 12)
  - Governments Documents (Box 12)
  - Governments Documents (Box 12)
  - Government Documents (Box 12)
  - Government Documents #1 (Box 12)
  - Government Documents #2 (Box 12)
  - Governmentt Documents (Box 12)
  - Government Documents (Box 12)
  - Forum for the Future of Higher Ed. (Box 12)
  - General Bookbinding Company (Box 12)
  - Goals (Box 12)
  - Government Documents (Box 12)
  - Graduate Division (Box 13)
  - Graphics (Box 13)
  - Green East: Meyer Library Feasibility (Box 13)
  - Green Library (Box 13)
  - Griffith University (Box 13)
  - GSB Computing Environment (Box 13)
  - Hamilton, Edward Norse (Box 13)
  - Hannon, Michael (Box 13)
  - HEA Funding for CA Institutions (Box 13)
  - Heffner Library (Applied Physics) (Box 13)
  - Henderson, Albert (Box 13)
  - Heraud, Jorge (Box 13)
  - Hilton, Ronald (Box 13)
  - HotJava (Box 13)
  - HOTNET: Hist. of Tech. Network (Box 13)
  - Green East (Box 13)
  - Guidelines (Box 13)
  - Higher Education Act (Box 13)
  - HEA IIC (Box 13)
  - HEA IIA (1981-82) (Box 13)
  - HEA II-C Manuscripts (1983-84) (Box 13)
  - HEA II- C Manuscripts (1984-85) (Box 13)
  - HEA IIC (Music) 1985-1986 (Box 13)
  - HEA IIC- Music Recon '86/87 (Box 13)
  - HEA IIC Music (1988-89) (Box 13)
  - Hilton, Ronald (Box 13)
  - Grants (Box 13)
  - Home Computers (Box 13)
  - HOTS (Box 13)
  - HOTS (Box 13)
  - Gross Fund (Box 13)
  - Hammer, Armand (Box 13)
  - Hiller, Stanley (Box 13)
  - Howard, Mrs. J. R (Box 13)
  - Kenneth Dowlin (Box 14)
  - Huang, Kung (Box 14)
  - Humanities/Area Studies (Box 14)
  - Hypertext (Box 14)
  - Hydock, James (Box 14)
  - IAG Meeting (Box 14)
  - IATUL (Box 14)
  - Imprint (Box 14)
  - Infrastructure (Box 14)
  - Infrastructure Advisory Group (Box 14)
  - Integrated Online Processing System (Box 14)
  - Intel (Box 14)
  - Intelligent Reference Information System Project (Box 14)
  - Interdepartmental Requests (Box 14)
  - Interlibrary Loan Services (Box 14)
  - Irvine Grant (Box 14)
  - Irvine Graduate Student Assistantships (Box 14)
  - Jackson Library (Box 14)
  - Jackson Graduate School of Business (Box 14)
  - JANUS (Box 14)
  - Job Descriptions (Box 14)
  - Kanazawa Institute of Technology (Box 14)
  - Kennedy, Donald (Box 14)
  - Kiosk Rollout (Box 14)
  - Lifelong Learning Network (Box 14)
  - Layoffs (Box 14)
  - Learning Environment (Box 14)
  - Letters of Recommendation (Box 14)
  - Lexis Nexis (Box 14)
  - Library Cost Allocation Study (Box 14)
  - Libraries and Info Resources (Box 14)
  - Logo Design (Box 14)
  - Lifelong Learning Network (Box 14)
  - Karen Nagy (Box 14)
  - Karen Nagy (Box 14)
  - LARCS (Box 14)
  - ILL/DD Task Group (Box 14)
  - Indirect Cost (Box 14)
  - Intellectual Property Rights (Box 14)
  - Internet (Box 14)
  - Koret (Box 14)
  - Library Materials Budget Model (Box 14)
  - Kaisel, Stanley (Box 14)
  - Martin Luther King (Box 15)
  - Management Development Program (Box 15)
  - Management Skills Workshop (Box 15)
  - Math / Computer Science Library (Box 15)
  - Marketing - Stanford Info. Environment (Box 15)
  - Math Library (Box 15)
  - Marquis Asocciates (Box 15)
  - Math / Computer Sciences (Box 15)
  - McChesney, Brooks (Box 15)
  - McKittrick, Bruce (Box 15)
  - MedBiquitous (Box 15)
  - Media Services Center (Box 15)
  - Mediaweaver (Box 15)
  - Medscope (Box 15)
  - Menlo College (Box 15)
  - Mentoring (Box 15)
  - Meyer Library, Fred Charitable Trust (Box 15)
  - Meyer Library (Box 15)
  - Meyer Library (Box 15)
  - Meyer Library (Box 15)
  - Michigan/MIT/Stanford (Box 15)
  - Micropublications (Box 15)
  - Milford, Charles (Box 15)
  - Millenium (Box 15)
  - Miller, Harold A. Library (Box 15)
  - Mindlin, Jose (Box 15)
  - Minority Interns (Box 15)
  - Minority Interns (Box 15)
  - MIP Survey (Box 15)
  - Repairs, Misc. (Box 15)
  - Mitsubishi (Box 15)
  - Mixed Media (Box 15)
  - Multimedia Distributed Library (Box 15)
  - Modern European Languages (Box 15)
  - Modernitst World Project (Box 15)
  - Moiso, Anthony R. (Box 15)
  - Mota, Carlos Guilherme (Box 15)
  - Mudd Family (Box 15)
  - Multimedia (Box 15)
  - Munger, Nancy (Box 15)
  - Munksgaard Int. Publishers (Box 15)
  - Music on the Internet (Box 15)
  - Mrs. John Thille (Box 15)
  - MRDF Worshop (Box 15)
  - Mellon Foundation (Box 15)
  - Mellon - Preservation (Box 15)
  - Meyer Library (Box 15)
  - Mixed Media Task Force (Box 15)
  - Minority Business Committee (Box 15)
  - Map Cataloging at Branner (Box 15)
  - Maas, Donald Sutter (Box 15)
  - Mann, Arthur (Box 15)
  - Mead, Giles (Box 15)
  - Main, Mrs. Walter Douglas (Box 15)
  - Manson, Clara Sue (Box 15)
  - NIST Virtual Library (Box 16)
  - NLII (Box 16)
  - National Digital Library Federation (Box 16)
  - National Endowment for Humanities (Box 16)
  - National Humanities Center (Box 16)
  - NCSA Mosaic for Mac User's Guide (Box 16)
  - National Digital Lib. Federation Policy Committee (Box 16)
  - Near West Campus (Box 16)
  - Near West Campus (Box 16)
  - Near West Campus (Box 16)
  - NETCOM (Box 16)
  - NET Future (Box 16)
  - Netscape (Box 16)
  - New York Public Library (Box 16)
  - SUL (Box 16)
  - SU (Box 16)
  - Newsgroup (Box 16)
  - News Notes (Box 16)
  - News and Publication Services (Box 16)
  - Newscan (Box 16)
  - New York Public Library (Box 16)
  - New York Public Library (Box 16)
  - Non-resident Aliens, Payments to (Box 16)
  - NACERI (Box 16)
  - Naco Cost Survey (Box 16)
  - NCCP Paper (Box 16)
  - Near West Campus (Box 16)
  - NEH (Box 16)
  - NOTIS (Box 16)
  - NOTIS (Box 16)
  - NOTIS (Box 16)
  - NOTIS (Box 16)
  - NTU (Box 17)
  - Oldano, Terry (Box 17)
  - Online Summit (Box 17)
  - Organization Charts (Box 17)
  - Overseas Studies Programs (Box 17)
  - Outsourcing (Box 17)
  - Overseas Campus (Box 17)
  - Office of Development - OOD (Box 17)
  - OOD (Box 17)
  - OOD (Box 17)
  - Office Procedures (Box 17)
  - Opportunity Fund (Box 17)
  - Organizational Charts (Box 17)
  - NOTIS (Box 17)
  - NOTIS (Box 17)
  - NOTIS (Box 17)
  - NOTIS Governing Group (Box 17)
  - NPG (Box 17)
  - NOTIS Project Team (Box 17)
  - NOTIS Project Team (Box 17)
  - NOTIS Project Team (Box 17)
  - NOTIS Project Team (Box 17)
  - NREN (Box 17)
  - OCLC (Box 17)
  - OCLC (Box 17)
  - OCLC (Box 17)
  - OCLC (Box 17)
  - OCLC (Box 17)
  - Optiram (Box 17)
  - O'Brien, James E. (Box 17)
  - Panas, Jerry (Box 18)
  - Parent's Weekend (Box 18)
  - Pensare (Box 18)
  - Parking (Box 18)
  - Pentium Computers (Box 18)
  - Parking (Box 18)
  - Perrette Book Fund (Box 18)
  - PCARD 1997 (Box 18)
  - Peters, Stanley (Box 18)
  - Petty Cash 1993 (Box 18)
  - Petty Cash 1994-1995 (Box 18)
  - Philosophy Department (Box 18)
  - Pilot Compensation Pro (Box 18)
  - Police Department (Box 18)
  - Polish Art Book Symposium (Box 18)
  - Portfolio Project (Box 18)
  - Physics Library (Box 18)
  - Physics Library (Box 18)
  - PRELECT Presentation (Box 18)
  - Planned Giving (Box 18)
  - Pledge Letters (Box 18)
  - Postcards (Box 18)
  - Portfolio (Box 18)
  - Personnel Department (Box 18)
  - Personnel Policies (Box 18)
  - Personnel Policies (Box 18)
  - Personnel Policies (Box 18)
  - PSG Task Group (Box 19)
  - Project Mandarin (Box 19)
  - Property Management (Box 19)
  - Preservation - Microfilming (Box 19)
  - President's House (Box 19)
  - Presidential Lectures and Symposia (Box 19)
  - Public Access Computer Systems (Box 19)
  - Public Affairs Council (Box 19)
  - Public Reference Services (Box 19)
  - Professorship Roster (Box 19)
  - Proposed Foundation to Support Computing History (Box 19)
  - Production Control (Box 19)
  - Proposal Samples (Box 19)
  - Proposals (Box 19)
  - Preservation (Box 19)
  - Preservation (Box 19)
  - Preservation (Box 19)
  - Preservation (Box 19)
  - Preservation (Box 19)
  - Preservation Office (Box 19)
  - Preservation (Box 19)
  - Pub Plan (Box 19)
  - Preservation (Box 19)
  - Preservation (Box 19)
  - Preservation (Box 19)
  - Preservation (Box 19)
  - Preservation (Box 19)
  - Preservation Office (Box 19)
  - Preservation (Box 19)
  - Preservation (Box 19)
  - Preservation (Box 19)
  - Public Services Group (Box 20)
  - Public Services (Box 20)
  - Public Services - General (Box 20)
  - Publicity (Box 20)
  - Publicity (Box 20)
  - RAMUS Project (Box 20)
  - Queen's University (Box 20)
  - Rebel Poets (Box 20)
  - Reference Department Scandal (Box 20)
  - Research Publications International (Box 20)
  - Risk Management (Box 20)
  - Public Service (Box 20)
  - Publications (Box 20)
  - Retrospective Conversion (Box 20)
  - Public Services (Box 20)
  - Reference Retreat (Box 20)
  - Retrospective Conversion (Box 20)
  - Recon (Box 20)
  - Recon (Box 20)
  - Retrospective Conversion (Box 20)
  - Retrospective Conversion (Box 20)
  - Retrospective Conversion (Box 20)
  - Retrospective Conversion (Box 20)
  - Robertson, James (Box 21)
  - Roxburghe Club (Box 21)
  - Rozkuszka, David (Box 21)
  - Roy Swank (Box 21)
  - Rotunda Exhibits (Box 21)
  - Roxburghe / Zamorano (Box 21)
  - RLG General (Box 21)
  - RLG General (Box 21)
  - RLG General (Box 21)
  - RLG General (Box 21)
  - RLG General (Box 21)
  - RLG (Box 21)
  - RLG (Box 21)
  - RLG (Box 21)
  - RLG Computer Files Task Force (Box 21)
  - RLG (Box 21)
  - RLG (Box 21)
  - RLG (Box 21)
  - RLG (Box 21)
  - RLIN Record Task Force (Box 21)
  - RTSD Collection Management and Development Committee (Box 21)
  - RTSD Guidelines (Box 21)
  - RTSD Publications Committee (Box 21)
  - RTSD Publications Committee #2 (Box 21)
  - RTSD Publications Committee (Box 21)
  - RTSD Publications Committee (Box 21)
  - RTSD (American Association) (Box 21)
  - Staff Compensation, Assessment of (Box 22)
  - San Francisco Book Fair (Box 22)
  - Saur, Klaus G. (Box 22)
  - Scanners (Box 22)
  - Schoenberg Archive (Box 22)
  - School Management Group (Box 22)
  - Science Discussion Group (Box 22)
  - Searcher (Box 22)
  - Senate 1997 (Box 22)
  - Senate (Box 22)
  - Serials Review (Box 22)
  - SGML (Box 22)
  - SLAC Library (Box 22)
  - SJC-R Governing Committee (Box 22)
  - Social Sciences (Box 22)
  - Society for Scholarly Publishing (Box 22)
  - Sponsored Projects (Box 22)
  - Springer-Verlag (Box 22)
  - Staff/Pres Reception (Box 22)
  - South Africa (Box 22)
  - Staff Benefits (Box 22)
  - Staff Association (Box 22)
  - Staff Development 1980-1983 (Box 22)
  - Staff Asocciation (Box 22)
  - Senate (Box 22)
  - Senate (Box 22)
  - SAL (Box 22)
  - Safety (Box 22)
  - Schmude (Box 22)
  - Science Department (Box 22)
  - Serials Department (Box 22)
  - Serials Department (Box 22)
  - Serials Department (Box 22)
  - Serials Department (Box 22)
  - Set Processing (Box 22)
  - Sexual Harassment (Box 22)
  - Shelf List (Box 22)
  - Sister-Libraries Concept (Box 22)
  - SLAC (Box 22)
  - Slavic (Box 22)
  - Socrates (Box 22)
  - Special Collections (Box 22)
  - Sponsored Projects (Box 22)
  - Staff Development Report (Box 22)
  - Staff Training Assistance Program (Box 22)
  - Serials (Box 22)
  - Stanford Centennial Campaign (Box 23)
  - Swain Library (Box 23)
  - Survey of Courseware (Box 23)
  - Systems Office (Box 23)
  - SUL (Box 23)
  - Stanford Integrated Digital Library Project (Box 23)
  - Stanford Instructional TV Network (Box 23)
  - Stanford Instructional TV Network and Cable (Box 23)
  - Stanford Library Literature Retrieval Service (Box 23)
  - Stanford Bookstore (Box 23)
  - Stanford Commemorative Stamp (Box 23)
  - Stanford Daily (Box 23)
  - Stanford Medical Library (Box 23)
  - Stanford Linnear Accelerator (Box 23)
  - Stanford News Service (Box 23)
  - Stanford Management Company (Box 23)
  - Stanford Self-Study Report (Box 23)
  - Stanford University (Box 23)
  - Stanford Publications (Box 23)
  - Stanford Statistics (Box 23)
  - Stegner, Wallace (Box 23)
  - Stormer, Gerry (Box 23)
  - STARS (Box 23)
  - Statistics (Box 23)
  - Statistics (Box 23)
  - Strategic Planning (Box 23)
  - Street, Bob Party (Box 23)
  - Student Assistantships (Box 23)
  - Summer Bulletin (Box 23)
  - SUFIN (Box 23)
  - SUL Anniversaries (Box 23)
  - SUL Bibliographers (Box 23)
  - SUL Directories (Box 23)
  - SUL Directors' Meetings (Box 23)
  - SUL Tuition Reimbursement (Box 23)
  - SU Museum of Art (Box 23)
  - Sullivan, David (Box 23)
  - Swedish Visitors (Box 23)
  - Swedish Universities IT in Teaching and Learning (Box 23)
  - System Development Foundation (Box 23)
  - Systems Office (1986-1988) (Box 23)
  - SULA (Box 23)
  - Student Assistantships (Box 23)
  - Stanford Data Center (Box 23)
  - SUL Budget (Box 23)
  - Stanford University (Box 23)
  - Support Staff (Box 23)
  - Systems (Box 23)
  - Systems Department (Box 23)
  - SUL (Box 23)
  - Strouse, Norman H. (Box 23)
  - Stanford, Donald (Box 23)
  - Taligent (Box 24)
  - Tancer, M/M Robert (Box 24)
  - Technical Processing (Box 24)
  - Technical Services (Box 24)
  - Technical Services (Box 24)
  - Technical Services (Box 24)
  - Tel-Aviv University Visitors (Box 24)
  - Telerana Project (Box 24)
  - Teltech (Box 24)
  - Temporary Employees (Box 24)
  - Training (Box 24)
  - Turbo Dog Software (Box 24)
  - Task Force on Disciplinary Reorganization (Box 24)
  - Trustees (Box 24)
  - Task Force on Information Systems (Box 24)
  - Technical Services (Box 24)
  - Technical Processing Group (Box 24)
  - TPG (Box 24)
  - TPG (Box 24)
  - TPG (Box 24)
  - TPG (Box 24)
  - TPG (Box 24)
  - Technical Reports (Box 24)
  - Technical Reports (Box 24)
  - Technical Services (Box 24)
  - Technical Services (Box 24)
  - Tech Services Throughput Data (Box 24)
  - Travel Program (Box 24)
  - Timoshenko Collection (Box 24)
  - Technical Service Information (Box 24)
  - Technical Reports (Box 24)
  - Technical Reports (Box 24)
  - University Archives (Box 25)
  - University Archives (Box 25)
  - UC Berkeley (Box 25)
  - UCLA (Box 25)
  - UCMI / Diversity Report (Box 25)
  - UC Northern Regional Library Facility Board (Box 25)
  - University IS Staff Reorganization (Box 25)
  - University Cabinet (Box 25)
  - University Cabinet (Box 25)
  - Undergraduate Studies (Box 25)
  - Ungroup (Box 25)
  - U.S. Department of Agriculture (Box 25)
  - U.S. HEW (Health, Educ., and Welfare) (Box 25)
  - U.S. HEW (Health, Educ. and Welfare) (Box 25)
  - UK Book Vendors (Box 25)
  - University Libraries (Box 25)
  - University Libraries (Box 25)
  - University Libraries (SUL) (Box 25)
  - University Libraries (SUL) (Box 25)
  - University Libraries (SUL) (Box 25)
  - University Libraries (SUL) (Box 25)
  - University Libraries (SUL) (Box 25)
  - University Archives (Box 25)
  - William Greer (Box 26)
  - University Library Council (Box 26)
  - University Library Council (Box 26)
  - University Library Council (ULC) (Box 26)
  - University Library Council (Box 26)
  - University Library Council (ULC) (Box 26)
  - University Library Council (Box 26)
  - University of Minnesota (Box 26)
  - University of Tokyo (Box 26)
  - University of Ca. Statewide (Box 26)
  - USC (Box 26)
  - Use and User Studies (Box 26)
  - USOE - General (Box 26)